

PROFILE

Energetic and compassionate individual committed to improving student learning experiences. Uses excellent curriculum knowledge to encourage, engage and inspire pupils to achieve learning goals. Approaches challenging situations with creativity and resourcefulness. Experienced teacher assistant with background in delivering successful strategic planning and policy formation. Committed to upholding school mission and values by analyzing student progress standards and addressing resulting challenges. Approachable leader with strong communication and interpersonal skills.

CONTACT

PHONE: 063 694 3695

WEBSITE:

developermoss.github.io

EMAIL:

dawmoss07@gmail.com

SKILLS

- App Developer
- Strong IT Skills
- Strong Maths Skills
- Problem Solving

DAWONE MOSS

QUALIFIED TEACHER

EDUCATION

Weslaan High School

2013 - 2015 Grade 12 Certificate

Boston City Campus and Business College

2017 - 2020

Diploma in Systems Development

Two Oceans Graduate Institute

2022 - 2022

Postgraduate Certificate in Education Economic and Management Science in Senior Phase Computer Application Technology in FET phase

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mulilo Mathematics Program - Team Leader

Jan 2024 - March 2024

- Provided guidance, support, and direction to team members.
- Created and implemented competitions to engage and motivate learners.
- Planned and executed Maths camps for grade 12 students to enhance their learning and preparation
- Assessed student learning and provided feedback to improve their understanding.

Mulilo Mathematics Program - Senior Teacher Assistant

July 2020 - Dec 2023

- Lead class under supervision of teacher and teach lessons developed for targeted academic enrichment.
- Assist mathematics teacher with all tasks required to smoothly run the class and effectively teach lessons to students.
- Created and administered tests to assess student learning and provided timely feedback.

Douglas SEDC - Assistant Teacher

Jan 2016 – June 2020

- Developed educational materials for students ranging from primary to high school level and partnered with teachers to implement in classroom.
- Worked in small groups with learners to provide better support.